Natalia Krzeszowiec

MANUAL TESTER, PRODUCT DESIGNER (UX/UI)

Get in touch!

Mobile:

+48 601 430 325

E-mail:

nkrzeszowiec@gmail.com

LinkedIn:

linkedin.com/in/natalia-krzeszowiec/

Github

github.com/natalia-krzeszowiec

Gitlab

gitlab.com/nkrzeszowiec

Behance

behance.net/nataliakrzeszowiec

Languages spoken

Polish - native

English - B2 level

Skills







SQL



Testmo



Gherkin



Dev tools



Github









Azure DevOps

Visual Studio Code

Miro







Adobe Illustrator

Ps Adaba

Adobe Photoshop



Da Vinci Resolve

About me

Hi! I've got 5 years commercial experience as a Product Designer and Manual Tester. I find QA very interesting and extremely important in the product development cycle process. Currently I am looking for a job as a Software Tester to spread my wings in this area!

Work experience

UX/UI Designer

OKE Poland | Jan 2023 - present

- manual testing of implemented components and functionalities
- · creating project documentation
- designing user interfaces (lo-fi and hi-fi) according to business guidelines
- creating and enhancing branding for OKE products (Civileo, Vileo and SPIN AI systems)

Product Designer (UI)

STX Next | Sep 2023 - Jan 2023

- creating user interfaces and developing a scalable system design
- working alongside UX Designers, Product Owners and Developers for clients' project
- creating initial Product Design recommendations for clients with PD Team
- preparing project requirements with client
- manual testing of implemented components and functionalities
- · raporting bugs

Work experience c.d.

Graphic Designer / UI Designer

OKE Poland | June 2019 - Jan 2022

- · designing wireframes, mockups and user interface prototypes
- working closely with the development team to ensure compliance and deliver increment at every stage of product development
- · creating project documentation
- contact with the client and users to validate the project and collect feedback
- editing promotional clips for company purposes
- · preparing all visual materials for the needs of the company (both printed and digital)

Education

UX Design Weekend Bootcamp (445h)

infoShare Academy, June 2021 - January 2022

Google Analitics for Beginners (16h)

Google, November 2021

UI Design Evening Course (72h)

infoShare Academy, October 2020 - December 2020

Visual Elements of User Interface Design (16h)

Coursera, September 2019

UX Design Fundamentals (13 h)

Coursera, September 2019